getsgain.com 2010-12-26

# Gets Gain

## Your Privacy is Our Priority

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of our clients and those who visit our website. Gets Gain safeguards clients' information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the highest standards to guard non-public personal information about you.

We will safeguard any information you share with us. In addition, we will limit the collection and use of nonpublic personal information to the minimum required to provide you with superior financial services.We restrict access to your personal account information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. Gets Gain utilizes encryption, firewall, router, third party verification procedures and other sophisticated security software and hardware to help prevent unauthorized eavesdropping of and access to clients' confidential and private information.

To provide better service and a more effective website. We use "cookies" as part of our interaction with your browser. A "cookie" is a small, text file placed on your hard drive by our webpage server. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to determine who you are or your e-mail address. We use cookies to determine if you have previously visited our website and for a number of administration purposes.

We do not share information about our clients with any third parties for their independent use in marketing their products. We do not disclose nor do we reserve the right to disclose, any nonpublic personal information about our clients or former clients to anyone, except to other nonaffiliated third parties as required by law.

 ** _We follow the same privacy policies and practices for former clients as are described in this notice._**

| 

|   
---  
  
**USD/JPY testing 81.65 resistance**  
The Dollar has been boosted by PBOC's surprise rate hike, and USD/JPY recovery from 81.10 session lows has extended to test the last days' trading range top at 81.65. 

If the pair manages to break above 81.65 (Oct 15 high), next resistance levels could be at 81.85 (Oct 14 high) and 82.00 (Oct 13 high). On the downside, support levels lie at 81.10/15 (Oct 18 low/session low), and below here, 80.85 (Apr, 20 1.995 low) and 80.00. 

Oct-19-2010 02:11:00 AM 

Payment Processors  
---
